555 Third Street, Atlanta, GA 09876 d.rogers@youremail.com (123) 456-7890

Daphne Rogers

PROFILE

Dedicated accounts receivable (A/R) specialist with over eight years of experience. Knowledgeable in A/R practices such as internal controls, understanding B2B's, and credit and collections management. Excellent analytical skills with the ability to prioritize and meet deadlines.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Accounts Receivable Specialist

Rental Max, Atlanta, GA | November 2015 - Present

- Implemented new procedures for the A/R department, resulting in increased efficiency by reducing invoice processing time by 22%
- Responsible for training new A/R team members on procedures, policies, and duties
- Led company implementation from Oracle software to QuickBooks, completed within 30 days, without disrupting accounting processes
- Builds and maintains healthy customer relationships to ensure timely payments

Accounts Receivable Clerk

Roberts HVAC Systems, Atlanta, GA | June 2012 - October 2015

- Completed day-to-day A/R duties such as invoicing, researching discrepancies, and performed administrative duties to support accounting staff
- Set up new customer account information and entered data into the central database
- Responsible for completing monthly financial closing for the A/R department

EDUCATION

Associate of Science in Business Administration

Franklin Community College, Atlanta, GA September 2010 - May 2012

KEY SKILLS

- Advanced user of Microsoft Excel and QuickBooks
- Attention to detail and works well under pressure
- ◆ Excellent interpersonal and communication skills
- Accurate and fast data entry
- Analytical thinker with strong organizational skills

CERTIFICATIONS

- Accredited Receivables Specialists (ARS), IOFM, 2017
- ◆ QuickBooks Certification, NACPB, 2016